Saba Arefaine

arefainesaba@gmail.com |(206) 790-0371 Seattle, WA <u>LinkedIn|GitHub</u>

PROFILE

Highly adaptable and detail oriented junior programmer with previous experience in application support at a global logistics company interacting with users both internally and externally on a daily basis. Excellent customer service skills and a collaborative team member, always curious and ready for a challenge as I further my career in software development.

SKILLS: SQL, Git, C#, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, EDI, MS Office, APIs

EDUCATION

True Coders Coding Bootcamp - Online

Mar 2021-May 2021

Software Development

University of Washington - Tacoma, WA

Sept 2016-Mar 2018

Bachelor of Science Information Technology

Honors: Dean's List (Spring '17, Summer '17, Fall '17, Winter '18)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nanny, Seattle, WA October 2019-Mar 2020

Expeditors, Seattle, WA

October 2018-October 2019

EDI Support Specialist

- · Provide excellent customer service to branch personnel and clients
- Research complex issues for quick and effective solutions
- · Identify gaps and bugs to escalate to Analysts and Developers for resolution
- · Able to read and understand EDI translation maps
- · Run SQL queries to identify data discrepancies

Earned an award for my Attitude & Commitment within the first two months of employment

South Seattle College, Seattle, WA

December 2017-March 2018

Student Technology, Advice and Resource Support

- · Assist students with software and hardware issues
- · Provide computer support for students not familiar with computers
- · Maintaining library printer

Alki Beach Academy, Seattle, WA

April 2014-December 2017

Lead Teacher

- \cdot Responsible for organizing, engaging, and planning activities appropriate for children age 0–5
- · Plan and implement monthly lesson plan with team
- · Create monthly newsletters documenting activities
- · Communicate with both parents and supervisor one-on-one about daily activities/setbacks